Zemin Jin

E-mail : jinzm1982@gmail.comm MSN : lowrain@outlook.com

 Phone
 : (86) 13401019493
 Skype
 : jinzemin

 Gender
 : Male
 Marital Status
 : Married

 Date of Birth
 : 1982/3
 Experience
 : 8 Years

Address : Tongzhou District of Beijing Census register : Zhangjiakou City, Hebei

Profile

Proficient at .NET, C#, Sharepoint, Javascript, HTML, CSS, SQL, Web application development, know well and interest in Python and ios development. Work about 8 year's experiences in software development and really love this job. With strong learning ability, have great power on analyzing and resolving problems, enjoy on challenging to new technology and new field.

Skills & Tools

Language: C#, VB, SQL, Javascript, CSS, HTML, Python, Objective-C Web Server Framework: ASP.NET, MVC, Sharepoint, Flask

Web Front-end Framework: jQuery, Bootstrap, Telerik, EXT JS ORM Framework: EntityFramework, NHibernate

Database: SQL Server, MySQL

IDE: Visual Studio, Pycharm, XCode, Dreamweaver, Sharepoint Designer

Version Control: TFS, VSS, Github OS: Windows, Mac OS X

Work Timeline

Shinetech Inc. 7/2007 — Now

Advertising, training and software companies 9/2005 - 6/2007

Experience

Octant Business Management Suit

11/2007 - 8/2010 & 10/2011- 7/2013

Software Engineer/Shinetech Inc.

Octant was born out of the need to help organizations respond quickly and intelligently to proposal and contract requests. This product is based on Microsoft Sharepoint, contains 8 - 10 developer and tester. I participate throughout whole development processing and entire product from requirements analysis, design and implementation of functional module, WebPart/custom controls, page layouts, data access, iterative optimizing and defect repair.

Sharepoint2007/2010 + C# + Telerik Ajax controls + Javascript/jQuery + SQL Server 2008 + TFS/VSS

Janison E-learning Software 2/2011 - 7/2011

Software Engineer/Shinetech Inc.

Janison is an Australian corporation, supports customers through the creation and development of client-centered, innovative, quality e-learning solutions. Include two sub projects, require high skill and quality.

Deloitte Academy System: Leaded another developer and worked at system maintainance, functionality expanding, new version development.

ASP.NET + VB + SQL Server + Web Service + jQuery + ComponentArt AJAX controls

Player by Rule & JService: Cooperated with Janison worked for updating Janison's core library "JService". It's data operation layout using EntityFramwork + Autfac. As while, created WCF service part for "Player by Rule" project. That is a MVC 3.0 application and based on JService. There were much business logic, technology analysis and communication between me and Janison team for achieving more powerful product.

 $\textbf{ASP.NET + C\# + SQL Server + WCF + EntityFramework + UnitTest + Ioc by Autofac + jQuery + Telerik + DDD + UnitTest } \\ \textbf{ASP.NET + C\# + SQL Server + WCF + EntityFramework + UnitTest + Ioc by Autofac + jQuery + Telerik + DDD + UnitTest } \\ \textbf{ASP.NET + C\# + SQL Server + WCF + EntityFramework + UnitTest + Ioc by Autofac + jQuery + Telerik + DDD + UnitTest } \\ \textbf{ASP.NET + C\# + SQL Server + WCF + EntityFramework + UnitTest + Ioc by Autofac + jQuery + Telerik + DDD + UnitTest } \\ \textbf{ASP.NET + C\# + SQL Server + WCF + EntityFramework + UnitTest + Ioc by Autofac + jQuery + Telerik + DDD + UnitTest } \\ \textbf{ASP.NET + C\# + SQL Server + WCF + EntityFramework + UnitTest + Ioc by Autofac + jQuery + Telerik + DDD + UnitTest } \\ \textbf{ASP.NET + C\# + SQL Server + WCF + EntityFramework + UnitTest } \\ \textbf{ASP.NET + C\# + SQL Server + WCF + EntityFramework + UnitTest } \\ \textbf{ASP.NET + C\# + SQL Server + WCF + EntityFramework + UnitTest } \\ \textbf{ASP.NET + C\# + SQL Server + WCF + EntityFramework + UnitTest } \\ \textbf{ASP.NET + C\# + SQL Server + WCF + EntityFramework + UnitTest } \\ \textbf{ASP.NET + C\# + SQL Server + WCF + EntityFramework + UnitTest } \\ \textbf{ASP.NET + C\# + SQL Server + WCF + EntityFramework + UnitTest } \\ \textbf{ASP.NET + C\# + SQL Server + WCF + EntityFramework + UnitTest } \\ \textbf{ASP.NET + C\# + SQL Server + WCF + EntityFramework + UnitTest } \\ \textbf{ASP.NET + C\# + SQL Server + WCF + EntityFramework + UnitTest } \\ \textbf{ASP.NET + C\# + SQL Server + WCF +$

Finance Pad CRM System 9/2010 - 1/2011

Team Leader, Software Engineer/Shinetech Inc.

Leaded four members' team to develop a web system of managing bank data and client/machine(Windows CE7 tablet). Base on ASP.NET MVC 2.0, UI usages EXT JS + AJAX, persistent layout and domain model integrate Nhibernate + Sql Server + WCF, add needed unit test for quality.

ASP.NET + C# + MVC + SQL Server + WCF + NHibernate + AJAX + EXTJS + Ioc by .Net Unity

Health Technology Research 4/2010 - 7/2010

Software Engineer/Shinetech Inc.

This project includes four parts: a WCF message delivery system, a ASP.NET web site, a sharepoint portal and a MS CRM server. The web site integrates with Sharepoint and CRM is the data center. Message delivery system is a SOA project, it encrypt/decrypt, sign/verify and transfer between multi machines. The whole project of HTR shows users the services and products, provides content data search and manages customer relationship.

Established HTR web site and Sharepoint portal; Integrated HTR web site with Sharepoint portal user management system and CRM data; Researched and implemented

WCF message delivery system with another developer according to client's requirement.

ASP.NET + Sharepoint + CRM + SQL Server + WCF

ECatalog Products Management Suit

Software Engineer/Shinetech Inc.

This project was to build a products management suit for customs searching and seeing products in every category efficiently. There were many complicated business logic and data operations. Developed with responsibility for structure design, web page design, ASP.Net and database development.

ASP.NET + SQL Server + Javascript + HTML + CSS

EarthTone 7/2007 — 8/2007

Software Engineer/Shinetech Inc.

Built web page templates with DIV layout and CSS. Insure templates pages must be up to Web 2.0 validation strictly and easy to integrate into ASP.NET system.

Dreamweaver + Fireworks + ASP.NET + HTML + CSS

Web site development, system maintenance

9/2005 - 6/2007

Software Engineer

Worked at web development or company internal system maintenance in several corporations after graduated.

ASP.NET + ASP + PHP + SQL Server + My SQL + Javascript + HTML + CSS

Education

Hebei United University (Hebei Polytechnic University)

9/2001 - 6/2005

Received a Bachelor degree of the Environmental Engineering

English

CET4

Be proficient in reading and writing in English.

Interests

Music, Photo, Riding, Coding, Comic, Movie, New Technique

8/2007 - 11/2007